大学英语六级第二部分 听力理解
College English test band Six, part two, listening comprehension.
部分的方向
Section A. Directions.
在这一部分 你会听到两段很长的对话 在每段对话结束时 你会听到四个问题
In this section, you will hear two long conversations. At the end of each conversation, you will hear four questions.
对话和问题只讲一次
Both the conversation and the questions will be spoken only once.
听完问题后 你必须从标有a-b-c和D的四个选项中选出最佳答案
After you hear a question, you must choose the best answer from the four choices marked A-B-C and D.
然后在答题纸上对应的字母上做记号 其中一个在中间划一条线
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet, one with a single line through the center.
谈话
Conversation, one.
原谅我。摇滚音乐，对不起，我们是爵士音乐商店，我们没有摇滚音乐。
Excuse me.Where's your rock music section Rock music, I'm sorry, we're a jazz store, we don't have any rock and roll.
哦 你只有爵士乐 没有别的了
Oh, you only have jazz music, nothing else.
没错 我们是伦敦唯一一家专门卖爵士乐的唱片店
That's right, we're the only record store in London dedicated exclusively to jazz.
事实上 我们不仅仅是一家唱片店 我们楼上有咖啡厅和图书馆
Actually, we're more than just a record store. We have a cafe and library upstairs.
大厅尽头有个售票处 你可以在那里买到城里所有大型爵士音乐会的票
And a ticket office down the hall where you can buy tickets to all the major jazz concerts in the city.
此外 我们在隔壁有自己的工作室 为有前途的艺术家复制专辑
Also, we have our own studio next door where reproduce albums for up and coming artists.
我们致力于培养新的音乐人才 哇 这是很酷
We're committed to fostering new music talent. Wow. That's so cool.
我想现在已经没有爵士乐坛了 不像以前那样了 但你却在努力推广这种伟大的音乐流派
I guess there's not much of a jazz scene anymore, not like they used to be, but here you're trying to promote this great music genre.
是的 的确 现在大多数人喜欢听流行音乐和摇滚音乐
Yes, indeed, nowadays most people like to listen to pop and rock music.
来自美国的嘻哈音乐也越来越受欢迎
Hip hop music from America is also getting more and more popular.
因此 爵士乐的听众越来越少 这是一个很大的遗憾 因为它是一种非常丰富的音乐类型
So as a result, there are fewer listeners of jazz, which is a great shame, because it's an incredibly rich genre.
但这并不是说现在就没有好的爵士乐了 远非如此
But that's not to say there isn't any good new jazz music being made out there anymore, far from it.
只是现在的市场很小
It's just a much smaller market today.
那么你如何定义爵士乐呢
So how would you define jazz?
有趣的是 对于爵士乐并没有统一的定义 的确 爵士乐有许多不同的风格
Well, interestingly enough, there's no agreed upon definition of jazz. Indeed, there are many different styles of jazz.
有些人会唱歌 但大多数人不会 有些是电动的 有些不是 有些包含现场实验 但并不总是如此
Some have singing, but most don't. Some are electric and some aren't. Some contain live experimentation, but not always.
虽然它没有一个简单的定义 虽然有许多不同的风格的爵士乐
While there's no simple definition for it, and while there are many different styles of jazz.
当你诚实地听爵士乐时 你就会知道它是什么 唯一知道它是什么的方法就是自己去听
You simply know it when you hear it honestly, the only way to know what jazz is is listen to it yourself.
就像伟大的小号手 失去阿姆斯特朗说的 如果你问 你永远不会知道
As the great trumpet player, lose Armstrong said, if you got to ask, you'll never know.
问题是基于你刚刚听到的对话
Questions are based on the conversation you have just heard.
第一个问题 我们了解到女士商店的什么信息
Question one, what do we learn about the woman s store?
还有一个问题 关于爵士乐 男士说了什么
Question, too, what does the man say about jazz music?
第三个问题 关于爵士乐 女士说了什么
Question three, what does the woman say about jazz?
的问题
Question For.
你应该做什么来欣赏不同的爵士乐明星根据女人
What should you do to appreciate different stars of jazz According to the woman.
谈话
Conversation too.
今天早上是怎么到银行去的
How did it go to the bank this morning?
不太好 我的提议被拒绝了 真的 但为什么
Not well, my proposal was rejected, really, but why.
一堆原因 首先 他们说我的信用记录不够好
Bunch of reasons, for starters, they said my credit history was not good enough.
他们有没有说要怎么改进
Did they say how you could improve that?
是的 他们说在我还了5年的抵押贷款后 我将成为一个更可行的商业贷款候选人
Yes, they said that after five more years of paying my mortgage, then I would become a more viable candidate for a business loan.
但是现在 他们借钱给我太冒险了 他们担心我会拖欠给我的商业贷款
But right now, it's too risky for them to lend me money. They fear I will default on any business loan I'm given.
听起来不公平 你的商业想法太棒了 你给他们看过你的商业计划了吗他们怎么说
Well, that doesn't sound fair. Your business idea is amazing. Did you show them your business plan What did they say.
对于实际的商业计划 他们并没有明确表达任何立场
They didn't really articulate any position regarding the actual business plan.
他们只是看了我的信用记录
They simply looked at my credit history.
并认为这还不够好 他们说 银行对贷款对象有严格的指导原则和要求
And determined it was not good enough. They said the bank has strict guidelines and requirements as to who they can lend money to.
我根本达不到他们的财务门槛
And I simply don't meet their financial threshold.
也许你可以从其他渠道筹集资金 从更多的贷款人那里获得小额贷款
What have you asked for a smaller amount Maybe you could gather capital from other sources, smaller loans from more lenders.
你不明白 我只求 大小无关紧要
You don't get it. It doesn't matter the size of alone, I ask for.
或者我提议的业务类型
Or the type of business I propose.
这都是无关紧要的 每家银行要做的第一件事就是研究我有多少钱和多少债务
That's all inconsequential. The first thing every bank will do is study how much money I have and how much debt I have.
在他们决定是否借给我更多的钱之前 如果我想继续这个梦想只有我自己的生意
Before they decide whether or not to lend me any more money, if I want to continue ahead with this dream of only my own business.
我别无选择 只能建立自己的财务
I have no other choice but to build up my own finances.
我需要个人储蓄多20% 债务少50% 就是这样
I need around 20% more in personal savings and 50% less debt, that's all there is to it.
我现在明白了 很遗憾他们拒绝了你的请求 但不要失去希望
I see now, well, it's a huge pity that they rejected your request, but don't lose hope.
我仍然认为你的想法很棒 你会把它变成一个巨大的成功
I still think that your idea is great, and that you would turn it into a phenomenal success.
问题5到问题8是基于你刚刚听到的对话
Questions five to eight are based on the conversation you have just heard.
第五题 女士今天早上做了什么
Question five, what did the woman do this morning?
问题六 为什么女人的求婚被拒绝了
Question six, why was the woman's proposal rejected?
第七题 这位女士打算做什么
Question seven, what is the woman planning to do?